Soumil Dey

Professional Summary

Proficient in handling HR functions on a wider scale from sourcing candidates to managing them throughout their life cycle. Managing and catering to the management needs pertaining to Human Resource is what I'm experienced in. I seek for challenging opportunities too where I can use my management skills for betterment of the organisation.

Employment history

HR Executive, ISGEC Heavy Engineering Ltd.. Noida, Uttar Pradesh

Oct. 2020 - Present

Catering to the manpower requirements on the site and handling 3rd party vendors associated with engaging manpower. Ensuring proper regulation of Statutory Compliances along with fulfilling full employee life cycle activities are also a part of the job. Other activities involve creating 3rd party sanctions for new joiners, fulfilling manpower needs based on the assigned budget, analysing job rotation scenarios, assigning relevant increment and perks, handling employee grievances, following up on proper salary, PF and ESI disbursement of manpower via 3rd party vendors and adhering to respective labour laws.

Business Development Manager, Dxpert Edutech. Noida, Uttar Pradesh

Apr. 2020 - Oct. 2020

Customer Support Associate, iEnergizer. Noida, Uttar Pradesh

Nov. 2018 - Sep. 2019

Business Development Executive, SNVA Ventures Pvt. Ltd.. Noida, Uttar Pradesh

Jun. 2018 - Oct. 2018

Education

NMIMS, Mumbai, Maharashtra

MBA, Human Resource Management, Dec. 2021

GGSIPU, Delhi, Delhi

BBA, Business Administration, May. 2018

Personal info

Phone:

9250800277

Email:

rjsoumil7892@gmail.com

Address:

B2-1703, Panchsheel Greens 2, Uttar Pradesh, Noida Extension, 201009 (IN)

Skills

Human Resource Management



Project Coordinating



MS office suite



Communication

